## **PERSONAL INFO**

whitneyhung.hello@gmail.com +44 7407113062 48 Rochford Walk, E8 3HQ, London LinkedIn: whitneyhung

#### RESEARCH PROJECT

# Caffeine and the Effect on Dynamic Reading Attention

June 2019 - Sept 2019 LONDON UK

Measured covert attention with an eye-tracker. I discovered that caffeine affects attention orienting speed.

I worked through hardware and software problem solving and data transformation in a short period of time and recruited 30 native English speakers through web resources.

I generated random stimulus with Python and analysed as well as visualised my data with R.

This is the first research measuring caffeine and dynamic visual attention.

# PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

#### **Technical**

R | Excel | SPSS | Python HTML/CSS | JavaScript | Git Adobe Illustrator | InDesign

#### Language

Mandarin | English

#### SOCIAL SKILLS

# President, Taiwanese Society

Nov 2018 - Present LONDON UK

Founded the Taiwanese Society at Goldsmiths Unievrsity.

Leading a team of 6, initiated 7 activities in an year and raised funds for each of them. Fundings add up to £900.

There were 15-40 attendees to each event.

# WHITNEY HUNG

DATA ANALYST | DATA VISUALISATION

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Goldsmiths University / Research Assistant

Oct 2019 - Present, LONDON UK

Working on dynamic visual research, information processing and nerural activities. Responsible for research design, data collection and data analysis.

# National Taiwan University / Research Assistant

Jan 2017 - Aug 2018, TAIPEI TAIWAN

In a research in collaboration with Kyoto Univeristy about collaborative learning and social memory, I was responsible for data collection and data analysis and assisted in research design.

I created an experiement website with a javascript library and PHP. I conducted meta-regression on 60 past research studies and analysed data with R. I recruited 140 participants in 3 months. The discovery was how social learning and practice impacts and magnifies memory performance.

## IPSOS Taiwan / Market Research Analyst

June 2015 - April 2016, TAIPEI TAIWAN

Over the period of 11 months, I was responsible for quantitative research, managing the research timeline, coordinating different teams, resolving inquiries for the clients and providing insights for collected data.

In a team of two, the projects I involved in included improving Taiwan High Speed Rail customer services, an annually research for Kikkoman products and direct selling branding research of the greater China area. I created business reports and assisted Q&A sessions of the presentation to CEOs.

#### Amercan Institute in Taiwan / Intern

March - June 2012, TAIPEI TAIWAN

Responsible for updating parliament politician profiles for the US government, which entailed Chinese and English translation.

#### **EDUCATION**

Goldsmiths, University of London Sept 2018 - Sept 2019, LONDON UK MSc Psychology of the Arts, Neuroaesthetics and Creativity

Modules: Statistical methods, Advanced quantitative methods

Uppsala University Sept 2012 - Sept 2013, UPPSALA SWEDEN

**Exchange Student, Department of Business Studies** 

Modules: Organisational behaviour, International marketing

National Chengchi University Sept 2009 - Jan 2014, TAIPEI TAIWAN

B.A. Diplomacy, College of International Affairs

Modules: International law, Foreign policy, International relations

# **ACHEIVEMENTS & HOBBIES**

#### 2019 GIT 40 under 40

March 2019, TAIWAN

Elected as one of 40 girls under age 40 in tech on Women's day.

#### GetLerped - Computational Arts Pop-Up Exhibition

Feb 2019, LONDON UK

Presented a projection mapping project coded in OpenFrameworks.

#### Half Marathon

TAIPEI TAIWAN

Finisher of 2014 NIKE We Run Taipei 21k and 2018 PUMA Night run 21k.